velnetweb.co.uk 2008-12-18

# Velnetweb - Terms & Conditions

## Introduction

At VELNET UK LTD we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers as well as users of Velnetweb.co.uk  within the guidelines and regulations that governs our [services](http://velnetweb.co.uk/terms.php/). This privacy policy applies to the use of our website including the services and products provided through it and also where applicable what we do with the information collected from customers and users of the Velnet website. 

### Information Collected

You may be prompted to supply certain information when you sign up with us as a customer on through a request form online. This information usually includes personal information such as; 

  * your name, 
  * the name of your business, 
  * your postal address, 
  * email address, 
  * telephone number, 
  * fax number 
  * and how you heard of us. 

### Information Use

This information will be used in the management of our database and to enable us contact you about the service/products you have requested for. You may also be contacted via your email address in order  to send you one special offers. If you wish you may opt out from receiving these offers. We may also use your information for the purpose of research to confirm how effective certain sales or promotion is, but whatever we may use your information for you are rest assured that Velnet UK Ltd will not release this information to a third party for a fee or for free 

### Log Files

Velnet as it is common now in most standard Websites stores log files. This information may include your Internet protocol (IP) addresses, Internet service provider (ISP), browser type, referrer, browsed pages, date & time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse trends. We may use this information to administer our website and help to diagnose any network or server problems. 

### Cookies 

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files- "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognise your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired. If you do not want Velnetweb.co.uk or any other site to store cookies in your browser you may configure your browser NOT to accept cookies 

### Disclosing Information

Although Velnetweb.co.uk will not divulge your personal information to a third party, the following circumstances are however an exemption: 

  * In order to register a domain name we are required to send your name or/and business name, postal address and email address to organisations that formally record the registration; this information may be available to others via a "Whois" search;
  * If we are required to do so by law or a statutory body;
  * To a financial institution with whom we hold an account for the purpose of verifying credit status and / or validating financial transactions. 

Velnetweb.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy policy of other companies or website. 

### Credit Cards

A third party processes online credit card payment for Velnetweb.co.uk. Your credit card details given online by you is collected over an encrypted secure server to guarantee your privacy and data security. Velnetweb.co.uk does not collect or store your credit card details. 

### Links to other sites and banner advertisements

The velnetweb.co.uk contains advertising and links to other websites but no personal information is passed to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and you are advised to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information if you are concerned about your privacy. This herein described Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by velnetweb.co.uk. 

### Consent

Use of the Velnetweb.co.uk website and services indicates your consent to the collection and use of information as described in this document. Any changes to the document will be posted on this page. 

### Changes to this Policy

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

Copyright ©2008 velnetweb.co.uk - VelnetWeb Internet services, London N4.
